Nao Takeda

416-879-5515

nao@sevencontinents.com

www.ntakeda.com

https://ca.linkedin.com/in/ntakeda1

Objective

Full time position as a 3D modeler, sculpture modeler

Highlights of Qualifications

3 years+ experience in 3D modeling, texturing Can create detailed sculpture in Zbrush Adapts well to new tools and work environment Organized and self-motivated

Skilled in

-Maya -3DS Max

-Zbrush

-Photoshop

-Topogun

Knowledgeable in

- -After Effects -Illustrator
- -Microsoft office suites

Experience

- SEVEN CONTINENTS

3D sculptor for mannequins and visual merchandise

- QUALIA (3D game for iOS)

3D modeler and texture artist

- **STRATUM GAMES** (3D game for iPhone)

3D modeler and texture artist for environment props

February 2013 – Current

September 2012 - February 2013

March2012 - July 2012

Education

- George brown College (Toronto, ON) January 2010- April 2012
 Ontario College Advanced Diploma
- Prefectural University of Kumamoto (Japan) April 2005- September 2008
 Bachelor of Literature and Education (Candidate)